Previously on Revolution...
前情提要
Why'd you do it? 'Cause we needed him and you asked me to.
- 你为什么救他? - 我们需要他 而且你让我救他
You have to tell me where my son is. One thing at a time.
- 告诉我 我儿子在哪 - 以后再说
You set off a bomb in my town.
你在我的镇上放了炸弹
Your job is to keep our town healthy and compliant,
你的职责是保卫镇子的健康安定
unless you're not a loyal American.
除非你不是忠诚的美国人
You can't fix him. It's the training.
你治不好他 这是训练的结果
You cut him loose, he will kill us both.
放了他 他就会杀了咱们
You were so worried about trusting my son, when you should've been worried about trusting me.
你只想到不能信任我儿子 却忘了也不该信任我
You said your husband was Patriot high command? What do you want?
- 你说过你丈夫是爱国者高级指挥官? - 你想怎么样?
Where is the old ball and chain? I'd like to pick your brain about the nanotech.
- 那老家伙在哪儿? - 我需要你对纳米技术的知识
He's already onto the bodies. Aaron, it's only a matter of time before Horn is onto you.
他已经在怀疑尸体了 Aaron 很快Horn就会找上你
So where are they?
他们在哪儿?
I did not want to be right about this. He's one of them.
我也不想承认 但他们是一伙的
We got to get Aaron out of here. I'm Aaron Pittman! I'll come quietly!
- 我们得把Aaron弄出去 - 我是Aaron Pittman 我会乖乖跟你们走
Just leave her alone!
只要放了她!
Aaron, you have got to tell me how you do that.
Aaron 可得告诉我你怎么做到的
You don't have to be afraid of him, but it's not him you're afraid of, is it?
你不用怕他 但你不是在怕他吧?
Why don't you tell me what's going on, please?
麻烦告诉我发生了什么?
Where's Horn?
Horn在哪儿?
I haven't seen the son of a bitch in a while,
我有阵子没见过那混蛋了
but I'm pretty sure you know where he's holed up.
但你肯定知道他藏在哪
He's working.
他在工作
Always working. Working where?
- 总在工作 - 在哪儿工作?
You have no idea who you're dealing with.
你丝毫不知道你面对的是谁
Is that right? Horn's looking for you.
- 是吗? - Horn在找你
He's got men everywhere looking for you...
他到处派人找你...
and her...
和她...
and Pittman.
还有Pittman
and once he finds you...
一旦他找到你们...
know what he's gonna do?
知道他会干什么吗?
Of course I do.
当然知道
That's why I'm gonna find him first.
所以我才要先找到他
So let's try this one more time.
再问一次
Where is he?
他在哪儿?
I know, I know.
我理解 我理解
The bombing rocked all of us.
炸弹吓到了我们所有人
It was a tragedy and an act of cowardice,
那是场悲剧 也是懦弱之举
plain and simple.
就这么简单
And, folks...
各位...
We now know who was behind the bombing...
现在我们知道了幕后黑手...
the man who stood amongst us and called himself Stu Redman.
他就是我们中的一员 自称Stu Redman
But his real name is Miles Matheson.
但他的真名是Miles Matheson
You may have heard of him...
你也许听说过他...
General Miles Matheson of the Monroe Republic.
Monroe共和国的Miles Matheson将军
Now, we have reason to believe he was acting in retaliation
现在我们有理由相信 他的前任领导
for the execution of his former leader...
Sebastian Monroe被执行死刑后
Sebastian Monroe,
他正在实施报复
and he didn't act alone.
他并非单打独斗
He had an accomplice...
他有个同谋...
Aaron Pittman.
Aaron Pittman
Uh, yeah.
好吧
Matheson and Pittman pulled the wool over our eyes,
Matheson和Pittman愚弄了我们
yours and mine.
你我都是一样
My daughter also came to town with them.
我女儿也和他们一起来了镇上
She was troubled psychologically.
她心理上有些困扰
Some of you know that.
你们有些人知道
She had nothing to do with any of this. She and my granddaughter are victims,
她与此事并无关系 她和我的外孙女都是受害者
manipulated by these men.
被那两个人控制了
So, please, if you see them, report it to a U.S. officer.
拜托你们 如果看见他们 请与美国官员联系
I'm begging you, help me find them.
求求你们 帮我找到他们
I just want my family safe.
我只希望我的家人平安
They said they'd meet us here, they'll meet us here.
他们说了会在这儿碰面 在这儿碰面
Well, I got news for you, stay puft.
告诉你个事 淡定啊
There might have been a change of plan.
计划可能有变
What change of plan?
什么变?
In that this plan has gone to hell.
这个计划彻底砸了
Those Patriot sons of bitches were waiting for you. And we don't know what happened.
那些爱国者混蛋在等着你 我们不知道出了什么事
We don't know if Miles can even get out of town or if he's still alive.
不知道Miles能不能出镇 连死活也不知道
We're gonna wait right here like Miles told us to.
我们就像Miles说的那样 在这儿等着
Okay,whoa, okay, okay.
行 哎呀 行
Just don't light me on fire or anything.
别把我点着了啥的就好
Who's that?
那是谁?
Nobody.
没谁
Just some intel.
情报来源而已
What's it like out there?
外面怎么样?
It's not good. Truman told everyone who Miles really is.
不好 Truman把Miles真实身份公之于众了
Said that Miles is the one that blew up the building and that he's the terrorist.
还说是Miles炸了大楼 是恐怖分子
Did you see your grandfather?
看见你外公了吗?
- Charlie? - Yeah.
- Charlie? - 嗯
Look, mom, we got to find a way out of town now.
妈妈 咱们得马上想法出镇
Not yet. Why not? Aaron's waiting for us.
- 还不行 - 为什么? Aaron还等着呢
This is for Aaron, trust me.
就是为了Aaron 相信我
They will never give up.
他们绝不会放弃的
They will never stop looking for him unless we kill Horn first.
如果我们不杀了Horn 他们就会一直找他
They're calling us terrorists.
他们说我们是恐怖分子
Just you wait.
等着瞧吧
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 革命之路 第二季第8集
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 革命之路 第二季第8集
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 时间轴：扫把不带星啊
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 翻译：黄先生 校对：酒囊饭袋 时间轴：扫把不带星啊
(GLENDON ART MUSEUM) PATRIOT REGIONAL OUTPOST
北卡罗莱纳州 Glendon 爱国者地区警戒部队
Hold it right there.
站住
Tom Neville from the Savannah camp.
我是萨瓦纳营地的Tom Neville
I'm here to see commander Roger Allenford.
来见Roger Allenford指挥官
State your business.
阐述你的意图
Just... give him this.
只要...给他这个
Tell him...
告诉他...
I only speak to him.
我只和他谈话
Those real?
是真迹?
A little privacy, gentlemen.
先下去吧 先生们
Is she alive?
她还活着?
Yes, sir.
是的 先生
She is.
活着
Where is she? Tied up...
- 她在哪儿? - 被绑着...
safe, hidden.
藏着 很安全
You've got a lot of balls coming into my office
你走进我的办公室 告诉我
and telling me you've got my wife captive.
你俘虏了我妻子 你很有胆量
With all due respect, sir,
无意冒犯 先生
your wife is an enemy of the United States of America.
你的妻子是美利坚合众国的敌人
I figured that you were a good Patriot.
我认为你是善良的爱国者
Am I wrong?
我错了吗?
She's guilty of sedition.
她犯了叛乱罪
She should be punished.
理应受罚
So why not bring her in?
为什么不逮捕她?
My guess is that you have
我是这么想的
a dark and stormy cloud over your head,
你有一项纯洁的事业
over an otherwise spotless career.
很可能蒙上阴影
I mean, your wife is a traitor.
我是说 你妻子是个叛徒
People have to be whispering whether or not you were pillow-talking,
人们一定在议论你是否吹过枕边风
whether or not any of it rubbed off on you.
你跟这件事情是否有染
But if you brought your wife in by yourself,
但如果你亲自逮捕你的妻子
delivered her unto justice,
让她接受正义的制裁
that would solve all of your problems, wouldn't it?
这些问题不就都解决了?
Turn that rain into sunshine.
坏事变好事喽
And why would you do this for me?
你为什么要这么做?
Honestly?
说实话?
I'm ambitious.
我有雄心
And I think there's value
我认为跟像你这样的人做朋友
in being friends with a man like you.
是值得的
So, Commander...
指挥官...
would you like to come and see the missus?
想来见见你夫人吗?
PATRIOT HEADQUARTERS
德州 Willoughby 爱国者指挥部
I thought these people trusted you.
我以为这些人信任你
I thought you were their beloved Dr. Porter.
我以为你是他们尊敬的Porter医生
Someone will know where Pittman is... I'll find him.
总有人知道Pittman在哪儿 我会找到他
Do you know what'll happen to your daughter if you don't?
如果找不到 知道你女儿会出什么事吗?
Or your granddaughter?
或者你外孙女?
Threatening me won't find him any faster.
威胁我也没法更快地找到他
Someone knows something.
总有人知道些什么
How about we get everyone Pittman knows,
不如把每个认识Pittman的都找来
march them into town square, and start executing them?
赶到镇广场上 给他们上刑
I bet they'll talk then.
那样肯定能开口
I have put a hell of a lot of time into managing this town.
我花了一大把的时间来管理这个镇
We have a plan.
我们有计划
Right, the plan...
对 那计划...
taking town after town.
一个镇一个镇地攻下来
And how many years until you take the whole continent?
你得花多少年才能拿下整个州?
If I get my hands on Pittman
如果我抓到Pittman
and figure out what makes him tick,
找到让他发作的原因
we take everything in months.
我们几个月内就能拿下一切
That's all.
就这样
Here, I found this.
来 我找到了这个
What is that?
是什么?
What is this, food?
什么 吃的?
People used to think so, yeah.
对 人们以前是这么认为的
I know you're angry,
我知道你很生气
and I'm not apologizing for him.
我也不会为他道歉
But you don't know why grandpa did what he did.
但你不知道外公为什么做了这些
He sold us out. He works for them.
他出卖了我们 为他们工作
Yeah, I get it. You hate him for it.
对 我明白 你恨他
You don't?
你不恨?
No.
不
Well, you're a better person than me.
你人性比我好
No, I'm not.
不是的
I hated you for a long time
我恨了你很久
for abandoning Danny and me...
你抛弃了我和Danny...
for killing Nora.
还杀了Nora
That's not fair.
这不公平
This is different.
是两码事
All I'm saying is hating you was the easy part.
我只想说 恨你很容易
But letting it go?
但原谅你
That's hard.
太难了
It's like EPCOT East Berlin out there.
外边就像未来世界东柏林似的
They have dogs.
他们有狗
When the hell did they get dogs?
他们什么时候有的狗啊?
You find the place?
找到那地方了?
The guy's intel was legit. Basement of the old paper factory.
那人的消息没错 就在就造纸厂的地下室
Definitely their H.Q. Is there any way to get in there,
- 绝对是他们总部 - 有办法进去吗
drop some kind of device? Not gonna be easy.
- 再扔点东西下去? - 不容易
Place is sealed up tighter than a drum.
那地方封得太严实
And, uh, Rachel, the...
对了 Rachel...
there's something else.
还有个事
I... I saw Truman walking in.
我...我看见Truman走了进去
Good. Two birds, one stone.
好啊 一石二鸟了
Walking in with Gene.
他和Gene一起
You should try to sleep.
你该睡一会儿
You haven't said a word all day.
你一天都没说话
Come on...
别这样
talk to me.
跟我聊聊
Did you kill Carl?
是你杀了Carl?
What?
什么?
Did you kill my husband?
是你杀了我丈夫吗?
The way he died,
他死的样子
the fire in the car,
车里的火
it was always strange.
一直都觉得奇怪
He hit me.
他打了我
Oh, my...
哦天...
oh, God.
哦 天啊
Oh, God, Aaron.
天啊 Aaron
I got angry, and I couldn't control it.
我很生气 我控制不住
You know I can't control it.
你知道我没法控制
You lied to me.
你骗了我
You murdered him, and you slept in my bed...
你杀了他 你还睡在我的床上...
and you lied about it.
你说了谎
I'm sorry.
对不起
I didn't know how to explain it.
我不知道怎么解释
I've had enough liars in my life.
我这辈子见过太多骗子
Cynthia...
Cynthia...
Just leave me alone.
别来理我
I need to think.
我要想想
What?
怎么了?
I always dreamed of cooking with my daughter,
我一直梦想和女儿一起做饭
just not like this.
但不是像这样
You sure this stuff is safe to carry?
你确定带着这东西安全?
Separately they're fine.
只要分开就没事
But drop this with this down an air shaft
但如果把这个和这个顺着通风井
into a locked up basement?
扔进紧闭的地下室
The gas will kill Horn and everyone else inside.
毒气就会杀死Horn和里面所有人
So when the time comes to do this,
如果到时候
what if grandpa's there?
外公也在里面呢?
Let's just hope that he's not.
但愿他不在
Okay, but if he is,
好吧 但如果他在
you're not gonna go through with it, right?
你不会动手的吧?
Mom?
妈
Where the hell are you going?
你上哪儿去?
You're just gonna leave us?
就这么扔下我们?
Look, if Miles was coming, he would've been here by now.
听着 如果Miles能来 那他早该到了
I'm gonna go find him. And what if they find us?
- 我要去找他 - 万一他们找到我们呢?
All right, just... just hold on, hold on.
行了 你...等等 等等
We wouldn't last three days without you.
没有你我们活不过三天
You think three?
你以为能挺三天?
Look, Miles has got some information that I need, someone I need to find.
Miles有我需要的情报 我需要找到的那个人
I held up my end of the bargain.
我实现我的诺言了
Now it's his turn...
现在轮到他了...
that's if he's even alive.
如果他还活着的话
You they won't kill.
他们不会杀你
Me on the other hand...
我就说不准了
What? What the hell are you doing?
啊? 你要干嘛?
Aaron!
Aaron
Aaron, help!
Aaron 救命!
Cynthia!
Cynthia
Help!
救命
Aaron!
Aaron
(MARCUS HORN) 18 YEARS BEFORE THE BLACKOUT
停电前18年
I walk through the valley of the shadow of death...
我穿过死亡暗影的山谷...
Dad.
爸爸
- I will fear no evil for thou art with me. - Dad...
- 有你相随 我无惧恶魔 - 爸爸...
She's not getting any better.
她好不了的
She will.
会好的
God won't take her from me.
上帝不会把她带走
What if there's something more that we could do for her?
如果我们还能为她多做些什么呢?
I'm praying as hard as I know how.
我在尽全力祈祷
Gary's father is a doctor.
Gary的父亲是医生
Maybe he could come and see her.
也许他可以来看看
- He... he could... - He could what?
- 他...他可以... - 可以什么?
We cannot control the lord's will.
我们无法控制上帝的意愿
Now, you know that.
你很清楚
Now come pray with me, boy.
来和我祈祷 孩子
The lord is my Shepherd. I shall not want.
主是我的指引 我摒除私念
We know that through you...
我们知道唯有你...
Oh, no.
哦 不
She can't.
她不能
It's her decision to make.
该由她来决定
Dr. Porter, what are you doing here?
Porter医生 你在这儿干什么?
We have the doctor to thank for finding you.
多亏了他 我们才找到你
Searching the boatyard was his idea.
是他提议搜查船坞的
Gene?
Gene?
Horn, let her go.
Horn 放了她
Please...
拜托
she's... she's got nothing to do with it. Please.
她...她跟这事没关系 求你
I'm sorry. I need insurance, Aaron.
抱歉 我得保险点 Aaron
Can't have one of your pyrotechnic displays.
不能让你在这儿放烟花啊
As long as you cooperate, she'll be fine.
只要你合作 她就没事
You son of a bitch.
你这混蛋
Let her go. Let her go. Cynthia, I'm sorry.
放了她 放了她 Cynthia 对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起
Aaron's inside.
Aaron在里面
18 YEARS BEFORE THE BLACKOUT
停电前18年
Dad?
爸爸
What have you done, Calvin?
你做了什么 Calvin?
Gary's father gave them to me.
Gary的父亲给我的
I didn't want her to die.
我不想让她死
Well, she died because of you.
可她因你而死
You prayed for a miracle.
你祈祷奇迹发生
But there are no miracles.
可奇迹不存在
Please, do anything you want to me.
想怎样对我都行
Just please let her go.
求你 只要放了她
There.
好了
That should keep you nice and relaxed.
这能让你放松下来
They tell me you came back from the dead, Aaron...
他们告诉我 你死而复生 Aaron
2 1/2 hours without a heartbeat.
两个半小时没有心跳
That would make you a modern-day Lazarus, wouldn't it?
你简直就是现代的Lazarus啊 (圣经福音书中人物 死后四天被耶稣复活)
That is, if you believed in that sort of thing.
你可能不信圣经吧
So what say we start
首先 我们不如
by seeing how resilient your body really is.
看看你身体弹力如何吧
- You're free to go, doctor. - I'm staying.
- 你可以走了 医生 - 我要留下
If you're going to hurt him,
如果你要伤害他
I want to be here to help him.
我想留下来帮他
How do we know pain isn't an important part of it?
疼痛或许也是很重要的一个步骤呢?
No, you did your part bringing him here.
不 你已经尽责把他带来了
Thank you.
谢谢
And as promised, as long as your daughter doesn't look for any more trouble,
按照承诺 只要你女儿不惹麻烦
I won't go looking for her.
我就不会找她
Now, doctor.
走吧 医生
GLENDON,NORTH CAROLINA
北卡罗莱纳州 Glendon
Jason, please.
Jason 求你
Please...
求你了
just let me go. Why are you doing this?
放我走 你为什么要这样?
Is it because your father's telling you to?
是你父亲命令你的?
Shut up.
闭嘴
You always follow the man's orders?
你总是服从他的要求?
I said shut up.
我让你闭嘴
He let you get shipped off to that reeducation center.
他任由你被送到再教育中心
He didn't try to stop it. He didn't say a word.
他没有阻止 连句话也没说
You know, he doesn't give a damn about you, and you just...
他根本就不在乎你 而你就是...
Jason...
Jason
you're not fully deprogrammed, are you?
你没完全恢复 对吗?
Not completely...
不完全...
not all the way.
不彻底
- How much further? - Just up ahead.
- 还有多远? - 就前面
Do we have a problem?
有问题吗?
Did you hurt her?
你伤害她了吗?
I wondered if something like this might happen.
我就知道会出这种事
You're still sweet on the woman.
你还喜欢那个女人
Well, first thing you need to know, I have a man on her.
你要知道 第一 我派了人守着她
You try walking in there without me, it'll be a short reunion.
如果我没跟你一起进去 你夫妻俩活不了多久
So how about we put the gun down?
不如把枪放下?
No, this is what's gonna happen.
不 不可能
You're gonna take me in there, and you're gonna let my wife go.
你带我进去 放了我妻子
And then? What?
然后呢? 怎样?
You two run off together,
你俩一起跑
escape like two star-crossed teens?
像落难小青年一样逃亡?
Boy, she must be worth it.
老天 她可真值钱
She must give it to you good and sweet.
她给你的肯定又甜又爽
Who the hell do you think you're talking to?
你以为在跟谁说话?
I thought I was talking to a man with his head on straight.
我本以为是在和一个头脑清醒的人说话
If I bring her back...
如果我带她回去...
they'll kill her.
他们会杀了她
You cut her loose and run off,
如果你放了她 跟她跑
they'll hunt you down and kill you both.
他们会追捕你们 杀了你们两个
How far do you think you're gonna make it
你细皮嫩肉 再拿点好画
with your soft hands and your fine art?
你觉着能跑多远?
Be realistic.
现实点吧
Your wife went rogue without a single thought
你妻子根本没考虑你和孩子的下场
of what it might do to you or your son.
就直接叛逃了
And if the boy has two traitor parents,
如果一个孩子的父母都是叛徒
what do you think they're gonna do to him?
你觉得他们会拿他怎么办?
The only question is,
唯一的问题是
what side of this are you gonna land on?
你会选择哪一边?
Charlie?
Charlie?
What the hell are you still doing in town?
你们还在镇上干什么?
You should be miles from here. We can't.
- 你们离这儿越远越好 - 不能走
Aaron's our family.
Aaron是我们的家人
How'd they find him, Gene?
他们怎么找到他的 Gene?
I found him.
我找到的
And what's Horn doing with him? I don't know.
- Horn对他做了什么? - 我不知道
He's still alive... for now.
他还活着...暂时
Grandpa, how could you?
外公 你怎么能这样?
They were gonna kill you if I didn't.
如果我不干 他们会杀了你
What else was I supposed to do?
我还能怎么办?
How about the right thing?
你可以做正确的事
How about everything that you taught me?
做你教给我的一切
Okay.
好了
We're gonna get Aaron out of there,
我们要把Aaron救出来
and you are gonna help. There's nothing I can do.
- 你要帮忙 - 我帮不上
You can't get in. It's too late.
你们进不去 太晚了
- And whose fault is that? - I was trying to keep you safe.
- 那能怪谁? - 我要保护你们的安全
Really?
是吗?
By lying to me?
所以你骗我?
By letting me think that I was crazy?
让我以为我疯了?
How was that supposed to help?
这有什么用?
Your mother...
你的母亲...
died of an awful disease.
死于可怕的疾病
There was nothing I could do
我无能为力
except watch her waste away.
只能看她日益衰弱
And suddenly...
可突然...
I had a chance to save everybody.
我有机会救下所有人
They gave me medicine.
他们给了我药
No one else had to die like she did.
不会有人再像她那样死去
I didn't realize who they were
可当我知道他们的身份时
until it was too late.
为时已晚
But, Rachel...
可是Rachel...
it's too late.
太晚了
You rolled over.
你倒戈了
You helped them.
你帮了他们
You've never done a bad thing for a good reason?
你没有出于好意做过错事吗?
What about you, Miles?
你呢 Miles?
Dad...
爸爸...
how am I ever supposed to forgive you for this?
我该怎么原谅你?
You're not.
不要原谅
I don't want it.
我不要
If keeping you alive...
如果保你性命...
means you hate me, then you just hate me.
会让你恨我 那就恨吧
But for God's sake, run.
看在上帝份上 跑吧
Run.
快跑
I know you all are in there!
我知道你们都在!
You got one minute to surrender yourselves and come on out,
一分钟内出来投降
or we're coming in.
否则我们就进去
Get them out, Gene, or else this ends bloody.
把他们弄出来 Gene 不然可就血腥了
You son of a bitch. I didn't know, I swear.
- 王八蛋 - 我不知道 我发誓
Look...
听着...
I can...
我可以...
let me stay behind.
让我殿后
Maybe I can buy you a couple of minutes.
我可以给你们争取几分钟
Please.
拜托了
No.
不行
You have to come with us. He's coming with us.
你和我们一起走 他和咱们一起走
Prepare to fire.
准备开火
What is this, Gene?
怎么回事 Gene?
Where are they?
他们呢?
Horn said he was gonna leave my daughter alone.
Horn说他不会再找我女儿
And he will.
没错
But Miles Matheson bombed the town, remember?
但Miles Matheson放了炸弹 记得吗?
Now, you hand him over, and your daughter walks free.
把他交出来 你女儿就没事
I heard that one before, Ed.
这话耳熟啊 Ed
It's the truth.
这是实话
Any one of you takes a step forward toward that building,
有一个人敢靠近这房子
this man dies. Big mistake here, Gene.
- 这人就死定了 - 大错误啊 Gene
I've made worse.
我犯过更大的
Go, damn it!
进去 该死!
Unbelievable.
不可思议
Why you, Aaron?
怎么回事啊 Aaron?
The nanites in your body are behaving in a highly individual way,
你体内的纳米机器人表现异常独特
repairing your cells,
修复你的细胞
oxygenating your blood.
给你的血液补氧
But why?
可为什么?
Why only you?
只有你这样?
I have no idea.
我不知道
You think of me as your enemy.
你认为我是你的敌人
But we're partners now.
但现在我们是搭档
You know, my father believed there was a magic,
我父亲相信 有一种神气的
invisible power all around us,
无形的力量 就在我们身边
and if he prayed hard enough,
如果他祈祷得够尽力
it would grant him a miracle.
他就能获得奇迹
He was a horrible, stupid man
他是个可怕的蠢人
who based his whole life on a fairy tale.
整个人生都建立在童话上
But it's ironic.
但也很讽刺
Turns out he was right...
因为他是对的...
sort of.
差不多算是
There is an invisible power that can save people.
确实有无形的力量 可以拯救人们
It just doesn't come from heaven, that's all.
只不过它并非来自天堂
But I have to admit,
但我得承认
it is, in its own way,
在某种奇怪的层面上
a miracle.
这就是奇迹
You're gonna teach me how to use it.
你要教我如何使用
I can't.
我不会
I don't know how.
我不知道怎么用
Then we'll figure it out together.
那我们一起搞清楚
It's important.
这很重要
I have a tumor growing in my brain,
我脑子里有个肿瘤
and the symptoms are getting worse.
症状在恶化
And I'd lost all hope. Then I heard about you.
我本来不抱希望了 可又听说了你
Aaron...
Aaron...
I need you to deliver me that miracle.
我需要你给我奇迹
And I believe that you can.
我相信你能做到
Jason!
Jason
Easy, boy.
放松 孩子
Everything's under control.
一切尽在掌握
Roger.
Roger
Justine.
Justine
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
对不起 真的对不起
Writing that letter...
那封信写得...
was stupid.
太愚蠢了
You knew how they would react.
你知道他们会作何反应
What they did to Max, to our baby boy...
他们那样对待Max 我们的儿子...
I didn't want them to do that to anyone else.
我不想让他们再那样对待别人
You know how much trouble you're in now...
你知道你给自己...
how much trouble we're both in because of you?
给咱们俩惹了多大麻烦吗?
I'm sorry.
对不起
You got to stay clearheaded about this.
你头脑可得清醒
Roger, this is a dangerous man.
Roger 这人很危险
You can kill them both, and we can run.
你杀了他们 咱们就能跑
Where?
跑去哪儿?
Huh? Where? Where can we go?
去哪儿? 我们能去哪儿?
Got to be realistic.
现实点吧
Roger...
Roger...
I love you.
我爱你
I love you too. Roger, no!
- 我也爱你 - Roger 不!
So how are we gonna get Aaron now?
我们怎么救Aaron?
And dad.
还有爸爸
Yeah, that's right.
对 没错
We're gonna go get your grandfather.
我们要救你外公
If either of you have any bright ideas, I'd love to hear them.
如果你俩有好主意 我洗耳恭听
So here's what we've learned.
这就是已知情况
Self-healing occurs as a direct reaction to physical trauma,
自愈为物理创伤后的直接反应
like a lizard regrowing its tail...
就像蜥蜴的尾巴能再生...
but your defensive actions,
但你的防卫反应
burning people alive and all that,
就是把人活活烧死什么的
are a response to emotional stimuli.
则是情绪刺激的回应
That's what the next phase is all about.
这就是下一阶段的任务
Here you go.
好了
This one should perk you right up.
这能让你立马精神起来
Aaron!
Aaron!
What are you gonna do? Sorry.
- 你要干什么? - 抱歉
I am, but we need to elevate you to a proper emotional state.
真的 但我们要适当提高你的精神状态
Then maybe...
那样...
maybe you can heal someone else.
也许你就能治好别人
No. Please!
不 求你!
You said you weren't gonna hurt her.
你说了不会伤害她
I'll check in in a bit.
我过一会儿回来
This room may not be the safest place to be right now.
这屋子现在大概不大安全
Stop!
住手!
No!
不!
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入